const level6questions = [
 
    {
          "question": "Add 3 to 33?",
          "options": ["867", "36", "69", "623"],
          "answer": "36"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 89?",
          "options": ["92", "795", "910", "79"],
          "answer": "92"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 446?",
          "options": ["449", "138", "710", "798"],
          "answer": "449"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 822?",
          "options": ["825", "977", "893", "525"],
          "answer": "825"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 174?",
          "options": ["177", "825", "947", "276"],
          "answer": "177"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 947?",
          "options": ["515", "291", "47", "950"],
          "answer": "950"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 177?",
          "options": ["180", "978", "971", "52"],
          "answer": "180"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 58?",
          "options": ["648", "890", "61", "213"],
          "answer": "61"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 871?",
          "options": ["874", "448", "639", "471"],
          "answer": "874"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 683?",
          "options": ["768", "461", "93", "686"],
          "answer": "686"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 804?",
          "options": ["807", "668", "212", "837"],
          "answer": "807"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 339?",
          "options": ["121", "342", "84", "29"],
          "answer": "342"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 571?",
          "options": ["88", "308", "422", "574"],
          "answer": "574"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 510?",
          "options": ["99", "156", "999", "513"],
          "answer": "513"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 774?",
          "options": ["622", "777", "827", "942"],
          "answer": "777"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 189?",
          "options": ["728", "192", "634", "700"],
          "answer": "192"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 153?",
          "options": ["513", "828", "156", "733"],
          "answer": "156"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 417?",
          "options": ["644", "810", "620", "420"],
          "answer": "420"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 397?",
          "options": ["880", "400", "545", "2"],
          "answer": "400"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 460?",
          "options": ["316", "92", "767", "463"],
          "answer": "463"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 826?",
          "options": ["861", "829", "358", "759"],
          "answer": "829"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 924?",
          "options": ["584", "915", "68", "927"],
          "answer": "927"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 597?",
          "options": ["305", "837", "39", "600"],
          "answer": "600"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 15?",
          "options": ["977", "42", "476", "18"],
          "answer": "18"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 646?",
          "options": ["977", "642", "350", "649"],
          "answer": "649"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 757?",
          "options": ["760", "193", "858", "284"],
          "answer": "760"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 538?",
          "options": ["511", "702", "541", "807"],
          "answer": "541"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 366?",
          "options": ["440", "369", "316", "671"],
          "answer": "369"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 678?",
          "options": ["314", "681", "875", "684"],
          "answer": "681"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 616?",
          "options": ["619", "987", "403", "751"],
          "answer": "619"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 485?",
          "options": ["976", "488", "746", "781"],
          "answer": "488"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 222?",
          "options": ["370", "250", "225", "501"],
          "answer": "225"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 91?",
          "options": ["94", "808", "689", "698"],
          "answer": "94"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 684?",
          "options": ["1000", "217", "91", "687"],
          "answer": "687"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 417?",
          "options": ["508", "420", "973", "239"],
          "answer": "420"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 171?",
          "options": ["874", "359", "495", "174"],
          "answer": "174"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 981?",
          "options": ["242", "269", "984", "46"],
          "answer": "984"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 598?",
          "options": ["501", "601", "461", "814"],
          "answer": "601"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 781?",
          "options": ["294", "784", "489", "782"],
          "answer": "784"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 107?",
          "options": ["32", "514", "110", "390"],
          "answer": "110"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 3 to 465?",
          "options": ["273", "490", "468", "977"],
          "answer":"468"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 422?",
          "options": ["365", "509", "671", "426"],
          "answer": "426"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 779?",
          "options": ["651", "838", "783", "615"],
          "answer": "783"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 472?",
          "options": ["554", "476", "805", "869"],
          "answer": "476"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 149?",
          "options": ["153", "658", "795", "548"],
          "answer": "153"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 163?",
          "options": ["167", "720", "473", "304"],
          "answer": "167"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 807?",
          "options": ["811", "128", "636", "398"],
          "answer": "811"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 236?",
          "options": ["768", "421", "240", "326"],
          "answer": "240"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 283?",
          "options": ["884", "886", "247", "287"],
          "answer": "287"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 335?",
          "options": ["339", "649", "1002", "107"],
          "answer": "339"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 202?",
          "options": ["206", "129", "626", "334"],
          "answer": "206"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 706?",
          "options": ["123", "947", "710", "311"],
          "answer": "710"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 605?",
          "options": ["609", "872", "285", "767"],
          "answer": "609"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 103?",
          "options": ["908", "381", "316", "107"],
          "answer": "107"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 743?",
          "options": ["747", "945", "276", "542"],
          "answer": "747"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 44?",
          "options": ["48", "570", "877", "342"],
          "answer": "48"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 341?",
          "options": ["345", "864", "810", "453"],
          "answer": "345"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 362?",
          "options": ["366", "260", "493", "447"],
          "answer": "366"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 314?",
          "options": ["318", "913", "962", "503"],
          "answer": "318"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 320?",
          "options": ["992", "978", "277", "324"],
          "answer": "324"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 328?",
          "options": ["595", "204", "332", "94"],
          "answer": "332"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 167?",
          "options": ["608", "188", "171", "37"],
          "answer": "171"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 863?",
          "options": ["40", "372", "175", "867"],
          "answer": "867"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 415?",
          "options": ["105", "692", "847", "419"],
          "answer": "419"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 231?",
          "options": ["480", "589", "191", "235"],
          "answer": "235"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 651?",
          "options": ["570", "899", "317", "655"],
          "answer": "655"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 344?",
          "options": ["344", "225", "348", "994"],
          "answer": "348"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 20?",
          "options": ["868", "19", "348", "24"],
          "answer": "24"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 870?",
          "options": ["841", "490", "874", "367"],
          "answer": "874"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 830?",
          "options": ["128", "641", "788", "834"],
          "answer": "834"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 859?",
          "options": ["968", "863", "8", "324"],
          "answer": "863"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 817?",
          "options": ["872", "821", "403", "183"],
          "answer": "821"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 135?",
          "options": ["139", "705", "458", "235"],
          "answer": "139"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 920?",
          "options": ["904", "737", "924", "999"],
          "answer": "924"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 272?",
          "options": ["256", "674", "276", "518"],
          "answer": "276"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 111?",
          "options": ["282", "115", "148", "78"],
          "answer": "115"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 148?",
          "options": ["952", "321", "491", "152"],
          "answer": "152"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 18?",
          "options": ["171", "405", "22", "995"],
          "answer": "22"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 580?",
          "options": ["660", "298", "584", "284"],
          "answer": "584"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 743?",
          "options": ["544", "356", "357", "747"],
          "answer": "747"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 248?",
          "options": ["252", "106", "867", "863"],
          "answer": "252"
        },
        {
          "question": "Add 4 to 923?",
          "options": ["83", "533", "414", "927"],
          "answer": "927"
        },
        
 
         {
            "question": "Add 5 to 610?",
            "options": ["615", "283", "956", "790"],
            "answer": "615"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 222?",
            "options": ["27", "227", "413", "239"],
            "answer": "227"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 905?",
            "options": ["910", "713", "331", "773"],
            "answer": "910"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 78?",
            "options": ["512", "83", "799", "575"],
            "answer": "83"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 330?",
            "options": ["35", "988", "335", "500"],
            "answer": "335"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 582?",
            "options": ["769", "251", "587", "7"],
            "answer": "587"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 905?",
            "options": ["816", "219", "910", "118"],
            "answer": "910"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 94?",
            "options": ["624", "99", "339", "696"],
            "answer": "99"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 559?",
            "options": ["586", "564", "723", "805"],
            "answer": "564"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 333?",
            "options": ["338", "892", "30", "687"],
            "answer": "338"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 927?",
            "options": ["1002", "667", "932", "138"],
            "answer": "932"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 73?",
            "options": ["161", "78", "110", "775"],
            "answer": "78"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 181?",
            "options": ["760", "186", "577", "837"],
            "answer": "186"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 880?",
            "options": ["844", "885", "141", "6"],
            "answer": "885"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 678?",
            "options": ["144", "717", "214", "683"],
            "answer": "683"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 476?",
            "options": ["480", "946", "481", "391"],
            "answer": "481"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 398?",
            "options": ["403", "56", "195", "63"],
            "answer": "403"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 162?",
            "options": ["930", "628", "479", "167"],
            "answer": "167"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 290?",
            "options": ["295", "666", "575", "159"],
            "answer": "295"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 402?",
            "options": ["561", "339", "13", "407"],
            "answer": "407"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 755?",
            "options": ["760", "545", "954", "70"],
            "answer": "760"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 17?",
            "options": ["554", "22", "964", "318"],
            "answer": "22"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 946?",
            "options": ["944", "781", "951", "142"],
            "answer": "951"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 839?",
            "options": ["768", "773", "844", "598"],
            "answer": "844"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 284?",
            "options": ["289", "18", "42", "335"],
            "answer": "289"
          },
        
         {
            "question": "Add 5 to 986?",
            "options": ["249", "899", "991", "533"],
            "answer": "991"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 719?",
            "options": ["498", "724", "942", "854"],
            "answer": "724"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 96?",
            "options": ["537", "835", "395", "101"],
            "answer": "101"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 235?",
            "options": ["304", "240", "608", "686"],
            "answer": "240"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 975?",
            "options": ["59", "980", "814", "727"],
            "answer": "980"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 960?",
            "options": ["965", "34", "196", "567"],
            "answer": "965"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 110?",
            "options": ["57", "902", "115", "775"],
            "answer": "115"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 675?",
            "options": ["412", "680", "885", "111"],
            "answer": "680"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 155?",
            "options": ["123", "160", "467", "15"],
            "answer": "160"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 849?",
            "options": ["784", "137", "854", "718"],
            "answer": "854"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 175?",
            "options": ["180", "778", "578", "317"],
            "answer": "180"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 559?",
            "options": ["564", "147", "21", "879"],
            "answer": "564"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 784?",
            "options": ["789", "992", "162", "360"],
            "answer": "789"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 946?",
            "options": ["929", "684", "487", "951"],
            "answer": "951"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 837?",
            "options": ["648", "268", "159", "842"],
            "answer": "842"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 812?",
            "options": ["19", "795", "817", "932"],
            "answer": "817"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 362?",
            "options": ["64", "674", "916", "367"],
            "answer": "367"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 767?",
            "options": ["680", "17", "772", "582"],
            "answer": "772"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 579?",
            "options": ["266", "584", "52", "789"],
            "answer": "584"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 842?",
            "options": ["735", "475", "847", "739"],
            "answer": "847"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 251?",
            "options": ["256", "426", "674", "99"],
            "answer": "256"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 806?",
            "options": ["96", "356", "416", "811"],
            "answer": "811"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 465?",
            "options": ["470", "867", "597", "951"],
            "answer": "470"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 742?",
            "options": ["747", "920", "468", "120"],
            "answer": "747"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 606?",
            "options": ["128", "83", "95", "611"],
            "answer": "611"
          },
          {
            "question": "Add 5 to 453?",
            "options": ["152", "73", "458", "204"],
            "answer": "458"
        },
        
        
       
        
];

export default level6questions;